

# Contact

#### PHONE

+46 737 26 7031

#### **EMAIL**

leesheppard2404@gmail.com

# **Technical Skills**

## **GENERAL**

JavaScript/TypeScript
Python

## **FULL STACK FRAMEWORKS**

NextJS Django

#### **BACKEND**

NodeJS

ExpressJS

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

**REST** 

#### **FRONTEND**

React

React Native/Expo

**HMTL** 

CSS

Tailwind

Bootstrap

## **TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGY**

CI/CD - Github Actions/FastLane

TDD - Cypress/Jest

**AWS - S3** 

Visual Studio Code

Git/GitHub

Docker

Vite

Atlassian's Jira/GitHub Projects

Mongo Atlas

Figma

Miro

Notion

# Social

## LinkedIn

**GitHub** 

# Lee Sheppard

# Full-Stack Developer

Originally from England and living in Stockholm since 2017 who has developed a burning passion for writing code over the last 3 years. I enjoy building web apps from front-end to back-end and overcoming the challenges that come with it as well as taking teams on a journey to our end goal, bringing out the best from each team member along the way.

# **Experience**

## September 2023 - January 2024

</SALT> - Stockholm, Sweden

# **Full- Stack Developer**

• September 2023 - November 2023 - Öppna Skolplattformen

Mob programming in an agile team of 3, working on a complete rebuild of the app, using React Native 0.72. Tasks included updating dependencies, building a CI/CD pipeline with Fastlane and updating READMEs making it easier to understand for future contributing developers.

• November 2023 - Present - Esthers.shop

Selected and placed in a team of 3, we have been tasked with reviewing code and optimizing site performance, so far we have switched all static images to a more modern format which has reduced the static folder size by 50% and optimized how content is delivered through Cloudinary's media storage.

## October 2019 - May 2022

United Parcel Service (UPS) - Stockholm, Sweden

#### Service Provider

Navigating a daily dynamic workload, effectively upholding levels of service to customers all over the Stockholm region

## May 2019 - October 2019

JD Sports - Stockholm, Sweden

## **Sales Assistant**

Working face to face with customers, delivering exceptional customer service to everyone who walks through the door. Striving towards each daily sales target by not only selling shoes but also upselling shoe accessories with each purchase while maintaining a visually satisfying shop floor

# **Education**

May 2023 - July 2023

## Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </SALT>

Intensive three month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning. 500 coding hours in 13 weeks. Passing every weekend code test and creating a stock trading simulation app - StockSense with NextJS

May 2020 - May 2021

## Full Stack Django with Python - Code Institute

Remote full stack development course over the course of one year, while working full time, learning the ins and outs of Django REST framework with Python